



Jun Kai

Fullstack | Blockchain Developer

ABOUT

A dedicated Software Engineer with seven years of experience working alongside different teams. I specialize in blockchain technology and responsible for collaborating with other colleagues on using progressive systems and applications, including accounting software, mass communication procedures and organizational apps. I feel myself as a powerful force in the workplace and use my positive attitude and tireless energy to encourage others to work hard and succeed.

SKILLS

Node	90%
Next	95%
React	99%
Golang	90%
Solidity	90%
Blockchain	85%

EDUCATION

2012 - 2015

Singapore-Institute-Technology
Bachelor of Computer Engineering

CONTACT

- coolsaki.ws@gmail.com
- (S) Ilive:.cid.526043c60c7599cc
- CoolSaki125
- CoolSaki#2522



WORK EXPERIENCE



2019 - 2022

Blockchain developer

Win-win

- -Worked on building trading view, swap modal using React, Next, TypeScript, Webs.js, and Subgraph.
- -Worked on building one chain, some tokenomics.
- -Worked on building Block explorer and Swapping site.
- -Developed automated trading strategies on Uniswap and QuickSwap.
- -Built smart contract with solidity and designed unit test with Truffle.



2017 - 2019

Fullstack developer

Tapin.tech

- -Designed Database with MongoDB and made API. Coded using HTML, CSS and JavaScript to develop features for both mobile and desktop platforms.
- -Designed and updated layouts to meet usability and performance requirements.
- -Produced websites compatible with multiple browsers.
- -Advocated for well-tested and documented, high quality code.



2015 - 2017

Frontend developer

OneTech

- -Architect product tours with React for a new feature that improved customer adoption by 18% leading to \$0.8 Min.
- -Professional experience building front-end web applications using React or another modern front-end framework, ideally using TypeScript.
- -Worked in a Test Driven Environment ideally with Continuous Integration and Continuous Deployment (CI/CD).
- -Worked on API integration, API payload preparation/processing.

ACHIEVEMENTS

01/2022 - 04/2022

09/2021-12/2021

HighLord

https://app.highlord.io

Metaverse

https://www.oppo.com/en/events/in noday2021/